# **JORGE SARRICOLEA**

WEB DEVELOPER AND UX/UI DESIGNER



#### ABOUT ME .....



I am a Web Developer specialized in UI/UX Design, with 2 years of experience working on different projects. I am a Personal Finance and Technology enthusiast, always keeping up with the latest trends, and have the ability to learn anything I set my mind to.

Check my own web page!

jorgesarricolea.com

WORK EXPERIENCE .....

## Co-Leader at En-Coders Programming Club | February 2023 - Present

**AAAI Student Chapter México** 

I teach programming algorithms in Java and Python, how to use Git and GitHub and operating systems to students on my university. (Non-profit).

#### Personal Portfolio | January 2023 - Present

GitHub: Portfolio-2.0

I am developing the second version of my portfolio, with an improvement in UI and UX, adding more projects that I have developed with JavaScript, HTML and CSS. **Go to my GitHub to check out all my projects**.

### Web Developer in Datamatic Software | June 2022 - July 2022

LinkedIn: Datamatic Software

I worked on the Front-End of an employee registration and management page for a United States company. Adding new features and connecting Air Table API.

#### Full responsive web app marketplace on Bubble.io | January 2018 - Present

jumwork.com

I designed the whole brand and user interface from scratch on Bubble. Integration with Stripe API and others in Back-End process. Work with differents plugins, like Sendgrid. I upgraded old pages to the new responsive engine.

## EDUCATION .....

## Instituto Tecnológico de Mérida

Ingeniería en Sistemas Computacionales. 2020 - 2024

#### **Platzi**

Interface Design Course. 2020 HTML and CSS Practical Course. 2021 Software Engineering Fundamentals. 2021 Frontend Developer Course. 2022

#### SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, JQuery, Node.js, Jest (Testing), Bubble.io, Java, Python, Git, Github, VSCode, Boostrap, Trello, Notion, Slack, Miro, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Figma (Mobile First)